<Document>
  # I.P.C.
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobIPCDummy" Caption="I.P.C."/>
  An IPC (short for Integrated Positronic Chassis) is a type of sentient robot and is considered an [color=yellow]independent individual[/color], meaning [color=red]they are not guided by any laws of robotics[/color]. IPCs cannot be hacked by Emags because they do not have to follow any predefined directives in their system. [color=red]IPCs are silicon-based beings, so they are healed differently to organic species.[/color]

  They take [color=#1e90ff]50% less Radiation damage[/color] but [color=#ffa500]50% more Heat damage, and 100% more Shock Damage.[/color] As they are Inorganic, they do not take Poison, Asphyxiation, Bloodloss, or Genetic damage, and Cannot Metabolize Reagents.

  ## Recharging an IPC
   <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="APCBasic" Caption="APC Terminal"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="BorgCharger" Caption="Borg Charger"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PowerCellMedium" Caption="Power Cell"/>
  </Box>
  IPCs can be recharged in three different ways:

  APC Terminal: IPCs can use APC terminals to recharge. Press [color=yellow]Alt + left click[/color] on a terminal as many times as needed to fully recharge.

  Borg Rechargers: IPCs can use borg rechargers to recharge. Always prioritize the ones outside of the Sci area to avoid headaches.

  Power Cell: IPCs have an internal power cell that serves as their battery. They can simply swap it out by opening the hatch and manually replacing it.

  ## Repairing
  <Box HorizontalAlignment="Stretch">
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WelderIndustrialAdvanced" Caption="Welder"/>
    Welders can be used to repair [color=yellow]Brute[/color] damage, alongside a little bit of [color=yellow]Cold[/color] and [color=yellow]Caustic[/color] damage, as well as stopping some [color=yellow]Bleeding[/color].
  </Box>
  <Box HorizontalAlignment="Stretch">
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ChassisPatch" Caption="Chassis Patches"/>
    Chassis Patches can be used to stop [color=yellow]Bleeding[/color]. They can be made by hand as long as you have Durathread and Steel, as well as being printable the Exosuit Fabricator and the Medical Techfab for cheaper.
  </Box>
  <Box HorizontalAlignment="Stretch">
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CablePack" Caption="Robot Rewiring Kits"/>
    Cables can be used to repair [color=yellow]Heat[/color].
  </Box>
  <Box HorizontalAlignment="Stretch">
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ComponentPack" Caption="Component Replacement Kits"/>
    Component Replacement Kits can be used to repair [color=yellow]Radiation[/color] damage alongside a little bit of [color=yellow]Shock[/color]. They can be made in the Exosuit Fabricator
  </Box>
  <Box HorizontalAlignment="Stretch">
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RobotStructPack" Caption="Robot Structural Repair Kits"/>
    Robot Structural Repair Kits can be used to repair [color=yellow]Cold[/color] and [color=yellow]Caustic[/color] damage, alongside a little bit of [color=yellow]Brute[/color] damage.
  </Box>
  <Box HorizontalAlignment="Stretch">
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="IPCOilPack" Caption="IPC Oil Packs"/>
    IPC Oil Packs contain coolant and lubricant and can be used to replenish an IPC's [color=yellow]Blood[/color]. They can be made in a Microwave with the right Chemicals made by a Chemist.
  </Box>
  <Box HorizontalAlignment="Stretch">
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ReplacementLenses" Caption="Replacement Lenses"/>
    Replacement Lenses can be used to repair [color=yellow]Blindness[/color]. They can be made in the Exosuit Fabricator and the Medical Techfab
  </Box>
  <Box HorizontalAlignment="Stretch">
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="OmniPatch" Caption="Omni Patches"/>
    Omni Patches can be used to repair [color=yellow]All[/color] damage. They can be made in a Microwave with the right Chemicals made by a Chemist. They are also found in a Syndicate Agent's Uplink.
  </Box>
  <Box HorizontalAlignment="Stretch">
    In the event an IPC dies, after being fully repaired, it should be restarted using the [color=yellow]"Restart"[/color] button (located by right-clicking).
  </Box>
  <Box HorizontalAlignment="Stretch">
    [color=red]NEVER ELECTROCUTE AN IPC with a defibrillator or in any other way while it is dead, as this will cause the battery to discharge energy rays outward![/color]
  </Box>
</Document>